Guide to the Cable 13 Videotapes, 1976-2009 UA.09.13.0008
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2016-0027, 1976-2009; 2
  - Cameron Corner #6, 1991 February 11 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0659)
    Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-044; Other notes: Thomas Hill, Virginia, Maryland, LSU
  - Cameron Corner #7, 1991 February 18 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0660)
    Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-045; Other notes: Pete Gaudet, Bob Harris, Jim Furlong, Mark Jaffe, Dan Bernstein, Announcers Comm. Gene - Women's basketball package, "The National Picture"
  - Cameron Corner #8, 1991 February 26 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0661)
    Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-043; Other notes: Bobby Hurley, NC State, Arizona, Announcers Commentary, Bob Harris, Mike Bernardino, Kris Olsen, Dan Bernstein, Jamie Rosenberg
  - Spaceman Spliff, 1991 February 27 (Box 46, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0662)
    Other notes: McIntyre
  - Cameron Corner #9, 1991 March 04 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0671)
    Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-030; Other notes: Grant Hill, Clemson, UNC, Announcers Commentary, Bob Harris, Mike Berardino, Mark Jaffe, Dan Bernstein
  - Cameron Corner #11, 1991 March 25 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0672)
    Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-025; Other notes: Jay Bilas, Conn/St. John's, Announcers Commentary, Steve Goldberg, Mike Berardino, Mark Taffe, Barry Jacobs
  - Young Guns - Duke Basketball, 1991 March 30 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0673)
    Program Length: 15mins5secs; Cable13 tape number: 9009-60-039; Other notes: 1990-1991 Final Four Highlight Video, Prod: Steve Goldberg
  - Shock The World Rock the Jayhawks, 1991 April 01 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0647)
    Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-026; Other notes: Final Four 1991 Steve Goldberg & Tim Kelly
  - Best of Under the Bridge, 1991 April 20 (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0648)
  - Inside Duke #1, 1991 September 29 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0698)
    Program Length: 30mins; Other notes: Soviet Coup, Panel, Primate Center, Bruce Nelan
  - 5:00 News with Chuck Crowder, 1991 October 02 (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0687)
  - TV Panel with P. Hartman #2, 1991 October 03 (Box 51, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0688)
    Program Length: 33mins55secs; Cable13 tape number: 2 of 2
  - The 5:00 News with Charles Crowder, 1991 October 03 (Box 57, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0689)
    Cable13 tape number: 8908-60-715
  - TV Panel - D. Hartman, 1991 October 03 (Box 102, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0690)
    Program Length: 60mins9secs; Cable13 tape number: 1 of 2
  - Live Football: Duke (17) vs. Vanderbilt (13), 1991 October 05 (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0691)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (3); Other notes: Live Van Production w/ 2 cameras and Video-toaster, Commentators: Seth Davis, Tyler Timko, Crew: Michael McIntyre, Greg Roth, Josh Shea Pepper, Susie Temple TRT:2:21:46
  - Live Football: Duke (17) vs. Vanderbilt (13), 1991 October 05 (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0692)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (3); Other notes: Live Van Production w/ 2 cameras and Video-toaster, Commentators: Seth Davis, Tyler Timko, Crew: Michael McIntyre, Greg Roth, Josh Shea Pepper, Susie Temple TRT:2:21:46
  - Live Football: Duke (17) vs. Vanderbilt (13), 1991 October 05 (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0693)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 3 (3); Other notes: Live Van Production w/ 2 cameras and Video-toaster, Commentators: Seth Davis, Tyler Timko, Crew: Michael McIntyre, Greg Roth, Josh Shea Pepper, Susie Temple TRT:2:21:46
  - Inside Duke Episode#2, 1991 October 13 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0694)
  - Chuck and Mike Show #2, 1991 October 17 (Box 57, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0695)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1; Other notes: Closing credits
  - Phil Nee, 1991 October 21 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0696)
    Program Length: 60mins; Other notes: Comedian - Griffith Film Theater, Crew: Macintyre, Weydig, Anderson
  - The Green Cathedral (A Video Poem), 1991 October 30 (Box 59, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0697)
    Program Length: 4mins24secs; Other notes: by Viavl Straub, Student Vido Piece
  - Chuck and Mike Show #1, 1991 November 05 (Box 57, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0674)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: Cool Visuals, Holocaust Scam, Crew: Jones, McIntyre
  - Chuck and Mike Show #1, 1991 November 05 (Box 57, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0675)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: Start 11mins into tape
  - Chuck and Mike Show #3, 1991 November 14 (Box 57, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0676)
    Program Length: 32mins8secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: Mike's Drug bust, Black frats, chronicle
  - Chuck and Mike Show #3, 1991 November 14 (Box 57, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0677)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: Mike's Drug bust, Black frats, chronicle
  - Talk to Me #3, 1991 November 14 (Box 59, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0678)
    Program Length: 35mins30secs; Other notes: Keith Hartman
  - Cameron Corner #1, 1991 November 18 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0679)
    Program Length: 60mins2secs; Other notes: Season Premiere, Coach K, Guest Announcers, Cherokee Parks Play, Steve Mitchell, Special opening - "Hoosiers"
  - 3 Cuckholds (Drama Production), 1991 November 25 (Box 61, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0680)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (3); Other notes: (no sound) Crew: S. Pepper, M. McIntyre
  - 3 Cuckholds (Drama Production), 1991 November 25 (Box 61, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0681)
    Program Length: 40mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (3); Other notes: (no sound) Crew: S. Pepper, M. McIntyre
  - 3 Cuckholds (Drama Production), 1991 November 25 (Box 61, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0682)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 3 (3); Other notes: (no sound) Crew: S. Pepper, M. McIntyre
  - Basketball: Duke vs ECU, 1991 November 26 (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0683)
    Program Length: 61mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 3 (3); Other notes: Seth Davis, Quinn Snyder Prod: Jones, McIntyre
  - Basketball: Duke vs ECU, 1991 November 26 (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0684)
    Program Length: 32mins55secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (3)
  - Basketball: Duke vs ECU, 1991 November 26 (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0685)
    Program Length: 17mins21secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 3 (3); Other notes: starts at 04:24
  - Chuck and Mike Show #4, 1991 December 05 (Box 57, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0650)
  - Cameron Corner #2, circa 1991 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0952)
    Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-046; Other notes: Hoops Highlights
  - Shadow Boxers Dub, 1992 (Box 59, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0055)
    Program Length: 30mins; Other notes: by Christopher Speck
  - ENO: Reflections on Eno River State Park, 1992 (Box 102, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0056)
    Other notes: by Michael McIntyre, Edit Master
  - Fuqua Follies, 1992 April (Box 58, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0724)
    Program Length: 63mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: Master
  - Fuqua Follies, 1992 April (Box 58, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0725)
  - Talk to Me, 1992 Fall (Box 59, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0729)
    Other notes: Editors of Duke Review, Missing Link
  - 3rd Eye Video 4, 1992 November (Box 59, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0740)
    Other notes: Prod: Michael McIntyre (episode won NACB award for best music video show, 1992-93)
  - The Christian Experience at Duke, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0760)
    Program Length: 43mins
  - Cross Purposes, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0761)
    Program Length: 24mins6secs; Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-010; Other notes: Ep. 1, Cliff Brinson, Vincent Gonzaga
  - Cross Purposes, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0762)
    Other notes: ep. 9 Father Mike Shugrue
  - Cross Purposes, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0763)
    Other notes: Special Segments Duke's Original vision, duke speaks
  - Cross Purposes, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0764)
    Other notes: Trailer & Opening credits Duke speaks intro
  - Blue Cheese, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0765)
    Program Length: 29mins28secs
  - From Da Group Home, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0766)
    Program Length: 60mins; Other notes: Ep# 3
  - From Da Group Home, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0767)
    Program Length: 60mins; Other notes: Ep# 5
  - From Da Group Home, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0768)
    Program Length: 60mins; Other notes: Ep# 6
  - From Da Group Home, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0769)
    Program Length: 60mins; Other notes: Ep# 7
  - From Da Group Home, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0770)
    Program Length: 60mins; Other notes: Ep# 8
  - From Da Group Home, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0771)
    Other notes: Ep# 9
  - From Da Group Home, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0772)
    Program Length: 60 minutes; Other notes: Ep# 11
  - FuquaVision, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0773)
    Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-047; Other notes: Nike Couch trainer, clip from tryouts, Cameos-orientation & ILE, 5:00 Tryouts, 8:00 Michael Porter Show, 14:45 Can't find a date to the Gala, 19:00 Powder Puff game, 22:45 Deloitte & Touche Disk, 24:35 Chapel Hillbillies
  - Best of FuquaVision, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0774)
  - In My Room Promo, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0775)
  - Duke vs San Francisco State, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0776)
  - Duke vs San Francisco State, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0777)
  - Kammerer Prize Videos, 1992 (Box 94, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0011)
    Cable13 tape number: copy 1; Other notes: 8 videos by Clark Mathis, Mark Paresky, Melissa C. Brody, Edwardo Morell, Lisa Klink, Eric Torkells, Heather Raikes
  - Kammerer Prize Video Entries, 1992 (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0012)
  - Duke Yearlook, 1992 (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0013)
    Other notes: Prod: John Vogel
  - Kammerer Prize Videos, 1992 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0014)
    Other notes: Clark Mathis "Sid Oakley," "All That's Left of You and Me" Mark Paresky "Six Speak About the Black Experience at Duke" Melissa C. Brody "In My Room" Edwardo Morell "Bastions of Solitude" Lisa Klink "Object of Power" Eric Torkells "The Sexual Karma of Laundromats" Heather Raikes "Whet"
  - Kammerer Submissions, 1992 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0015)
    Cable13 tape number: copy 5
  - Chuck D. and H. Allan Speech, 1992 January 29 (Box 61, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0731)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (3); Other notes: Page Aud.
  - Chuck D. and H. Allan Speech, 1992 January 29 (Box 61, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0732)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (3); Other notes: Page Aud.
  - Chuck D. and H. Allan Speech, 1992 January 29 (Box 61, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0733)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 3 (3); Other notes: Page Aud. Q & A
  - FuquaVision Ep #4, 1992 February 21 (Box 58, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0730)
    Program Length: 19mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-035
  - Inside Duke #3, 1992 March 01 (Box 57, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0734)
    Program Length: 12mins; Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-019; Other notes: "Spoiled Sports"
  - In My Room #1, 1992 March 04 (Box 58, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0735)
  - In My Room #2, 1992 March 11 (Box 58, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0736)
    Program Length: 54mins24secs; Cable13 tape number: 8811-60-618; Other notes: Roccofemia, Seth Davis, Chip, Geoff
  - In My Room, 1992 March 11 (Box 64, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0737)
    Program Length: 56mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #2
  - Cameron Corner #6, 1992 March 23 (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0738)
  - In My Room #3, 1992 March 25 (Box 58, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0739)
    Other notes: Wendell Theater Group, Chip, Geoff
  - "March to Minneapolis, The Duke Skywalkers", 1992 April 04 (Box 61, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0717)
    Other notes: Basketball Video, Crew: Seth Davis, James Rapp, Eric Jones
  - ASDU Presidential Debate, 1992 April 15 (Box 61, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0718)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (3); Other notes: Richard Moore, D. Kennedy, Hardy Vieux
  - ASDU Presidential Debate, 1992 April 15 (Box 61, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0719)
  - ASDU Presidential Debate, 1992 April 15 (Box 61, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0720)
  - From Da Group Home, 1992 April 19 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0721)
    Other notes: Ep# 12
  - In My Room #7, 1992 April 22 (Box 58, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0722)
    Other notes: Guests: Grant Hill, Ken Blakeney
  - FuquaVision Ep #5, 1992 April 23 (Box 58, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0723)
    Program Length: 21mins
  - From Da Group Home, 1992 September 09 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0755)
    Program Length: 29mins; Other notes: Ep # 1
  - Special Events: The Comedy Spot, 1992 September 17 (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0756)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: w/ Jonathan Brandt, Crew: Michele Cicale
  - Special Events: The Comedy Spot, 1992 September 17 (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0757)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: w/ Kevin Flynn, Crew: Michele Cicale
  - From Da Group Home, 1992 September 18 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0758)
    Program Length: 30mins; Other notes: Ep# 2
  - From Da Group Home, 1992 September 24 (Box 64, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0759)
  - Cross Purposes, 1992 October 24 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0752)
    Program Length: 31mins; Other notes: Ep.2 Christians & Politics Becky Baer
  - Fugitive/Hostage Situation at Duke, 1992 October 27 (Box 61, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0753)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: Hostage/Convict, Crew: Zimmer, Jones, McIntyre
  - In My Room, 1992 October 28 (Box 64, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0754)
    Cable13 tape number: R-3; Other notes: Assassins, Duke Dems, College Republicans
  - Inside Duke #1, 1992 November 01 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0741)
  - From Da Group Home, 1992 November 02 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0742)
    Program Length: 60mins; Other notes: Ep# 4
  - In My Room, 1992 November 04 (Box 64, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0743)
    Other notes: First 5 min 1988 Bamatide Promo Revised Edition
  - Cross Purposes, 1992 November 06 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0744)
    Program Length: 55mins30secs; Other notes: Ep.3 Debra Brazzel
  - Football: Duke vs Wake Forest, 1992 November 07 (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0745)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (3)
  - Football: Duke vs Wake Forest, 1992 November 07 (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0746)
  - Football: Duke vs Wake Forest, 1992 November 07 (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0747)
  - In My Room, 1992 November 09 (Box 69, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0748)
    Other notes: Circe Bermundy
  - Hour of Power, 1992 November 10 (Box 96, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0749)
    Program Length: 31mins9secs; Cable13 tape number: Show #1
  - Cross Purposes, 1992 November 13 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0750)
    Program Length: 57mins43secs; Other notes: Ep. 4 Dennis Darville The Meaning of Life
  - Cameron Corner Season Premiere, 1992 November 30 (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0751)
    Other notes: Guests: Bobby Hurley, Thomas Hill, Features: Inside-out, Running Down a Dream, Crew: Chris Collins, Tony Moore, Kenny Brown, Gene Gorman, James Rapp
  - Basketball: Duke vs Northeastern, 1992 December 07 (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0726)
    Program Length: 38mins44secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2)
  - Basketball: Duke vs Northeastern, 1992 December 07 (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0727)
    Program Length: 46mins5secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2)
  - Cross Purposes, 1992 December 11 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0728)
    Program Length: 55mins30secs; Other notes: Ep. 5 "Give Me an Answer"
  - Life on the Quad: Gourmand Gourmets, 1993 August (Box 66, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0780)
    Cable13 tape number: L14/S5; Other notes: Opening credits, shots and music
  - FuquaVision 1993-1994, 1993 Fall (Box 57, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0781)
    Program Length: 29mins45secs; Cable13 tape number: Ep 1 & 2; Other notes: Fuqua Links, Orientation, Seinfeld, Nowhere Man, Secret parking garage
  - FuquaVision, 1993 Fall (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0782)
    Program Length: 19mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: Ep #3; Other notes: Cameron Classroom, Decision models, Fuqua football
  - Madness.. and Other Pleasures, 1993 January (Box 66, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0788)
    Program Length: 40mins; Cable13 tape number: Part 1; Other notes: Dir: Jody McAuliffe Duke's Institute of the Arts, Crew: Shea Pepper
  - Madness.. and Other Pleasures, 1993 January (Box 66, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0789)
    Program Length: 25mins; Cable13 tape number: Part 2; Other notes: Dir: Jody McAuliffe Duke's Institute of the Arts, Crew: Shea Pepper
  - World Premiere Festival, 1993 Spring (Box 66, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0804)
    Program Length: 25mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (3)
  - World Premiere Festival, 1993 Spring (Box 66, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0805)
    Program Length: 11mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (3)
  - World Premiere Festival, 1993 Spring (Box 66, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0806)
    Program Length: 13mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 3 (3)
  - Basketball: Duke vs High 5 America, 1993-1994 (Box 57, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0807)
    Program Length: 52mins42secs; Other notes: Pre-season game
  - From Da Group Home, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0808)
    Program Length: 59mins; Cable13 tape number: Vol. 2 Tape 2; Other notes: Ep# 14
  - From Da Group Home, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0809)
    Program Length: 60mins; Other notes: Ep# 15
  - Black Butterfly: The African-Am Woman Speaks, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0810)
    Other notes: African-American Women discuss the African-American Man
  - Black Butterfly: The African-Am Woman Speaks, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0811)
    Program Length: 32mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #6; Other notes: African-American Man speaks about the African-American Woman
  - Open Minds: Sexual Assault, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0812)
    Program Length: 29mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #1
  - Film & Video Program Student Films, 1993-1994 (Box 69, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0813)
    Program Length: 59mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #1; Other notes: Tom Whiteside
  - Cameron Corner Opening, 1993-1994 (Box 71, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0814)
  - The Best of FuquaVision, 1993-1994 (Box 72, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0815)
    Cable13 tape number: Master
  - Reel 2 Real, 1993-1994 (Box 73, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0816)
    Program Length: 55mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #1
  - Reel 2 Real, 1993-1994 (Box 73, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0817)
    Program Length: 54mins33secs; Cable13 tape number: Ep #2
  - Reel 2 Real, 1993-1994 (Box 73, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0818)
    Program Length: 54mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #3
  - Kammerer Prize Video Entries, 1993 (Box 94, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0016)
    Cable13 tape number: copy 1; Other notes: 1."Indiscipline" Alexander Kort, 4:52, 2."Eno..." Michael McIntyre, 3."Convention '92" Chet Fenster, 4."The Resolution of a Modern Man" Julie Freeman, 7:30
  - Duke Yearlook, 1993 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0017)
    Other notes: Prod: Halim Habiby
  - Cross Purposes Commercial, 1993 January 23 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0790)
  - Cross Purposes, 1993 January 29 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0791)
    Program Length: 55mins30secs; Other notes: Ep. 6 Pastor Scott on Fundamentalism
  - Cameron Corner #2, 1993 February 01 (Box 64, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0783)
    Other notes: Guest: Marty Clark, Piece: Mrs. K (James Rapp)
  - Cross Purposes, 1993 February 05 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0784)
    Program Length: 58mins; Other notes: Ep. 7 Rice Brooks Champions for Christ
  - In My Room, 1993 February 10 (Box 64, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0785)
    Cable13 tape number: Ep 3; Other notes: Blue Devil and Cheerleaders
  - Cameron Corner #3, 1993 February 15, 1993 February 16 (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0786)
    Other notes: Round Table: Sacks, Robbins, Hoffman, Jacobs
  - Cameron Corner #4, 1993 February 22 (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0787)
    Other notes: Prod: Gene Gorman, James Rapp, Guest: Chris Collins, Round Table: Bill Brill, Dave Loyster, Michael Robbins, Moorari Shah
  - Cameron Corner #5, 1993 March 01 (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0792)
    Other notes: Round Table: Harris, Hoffman, Sacks, Robbins
  - ASDU Presidential Debate, 1993 March 02 (Box 66, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0793)
    Other notes: Crew: Michael McIntyre, Marc Morkan, Shea Pepper, Javon Nesbit
  - Cross Purposes, 1993 March 05 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0794)
    Program Length: 59mins; Other notes: Ep. 8 George Piwang :African Christianity"
  - Cameron Corner #6, 1993 March 08 (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0795)
    Other notes: Guest: Mike Krzyzewski, Prod: Gene Gorman, James Rapp, Piece: Mrs. K
  - Duke Chapel: Jesse Jackson, 1993 March 09 (Box 67, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0796)
  - Duke Chapel: Jesse Jackson, 1993 March 09 (Box 70, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0797)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2
  - From Da Group Home, 1993 April 04 (Box 63, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0778)
    Other notes: Ep# 10
  - Cross Purposes, 1993 April 24 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0779)
    Program Length: 57mins24secs; Other notes: Ep. 10 Joe Sarver
  - In My Room, 1993 October 06 (Box 64, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0800)
    Cable13 tape number: Ep #1; Other notes: Season Opener, Crew: Kenny Blakeney, Chris Collins
  - In My Room, 1993 October 13 (Box 71, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0801)
    Other notes: Dean Sue and Freshmen
  - In My Room, 1993 October 27 (Box 64, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0802)
    Cable13 tape number: Ep #3: 1 of 2; Other notes: Crew: Joey Beard, Jeff Capel
  - In My Room #3, 1993 October 27 (Box 69, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0803)
    Cable13 tape number: Part 2
  - Come As You Are: Pilot, 1993 November 16 (Box 68, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0798)
  - Cameron Corner #1, 1993 November 22 (Box 64, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0799)
    Program Length: 55mins; Other notes: Guest: Tony Lang
  - Blue Traveler - England, 1994 (Box 69, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0003)
    Program Length: 28mins
  - Men's Basketball: Blue/White Game, 1994 (Box 66, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0057)
  - Cameron Corner, 1994 (Box 73, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0058)